



Core Competencies

- Agile
- Svn Tortoise
- Jira
- mysql
- bootstrap
- codeigniter
- jquery
- javascript
- laravel
- ajax
- Linux
- Apache
- MySQL
- PHP
- Windows
- Javascript
- Codeigniter
- HTML
- Wordpress
- JQuery
- Ajax
- Oracle
- Web Services
- Rest
- JSON
- Yii
- · Rest Api

Patekar Ganesh Babasaheb

Senior Developer







"

Exposure knowledge of PHP development using Web-services, JQuery,PHP Framework like Laravel/Codeignitor, Yii 1.1, core PHP, Javascript.Bootstrap,Ajax ,HTML,CSS, Web services and total having experience of 7 years.



Profile Summary

Myself Ganesh Patekar, Age: 31, Done MCA with 1st class from Pune university 2015, here applying for PHP Full stack developer. I have experience in framework like Laravel / YII 1.1, with css, bootstrap, JavaScript/JQuery, Ajax, Web API. and also having total 7.0 years experience in this field.



Education

MCA, 2015

Pune University

bsc science, 2012

v p college vaijapur

12th, 2009

Maharashtra, English

10th, 2007

Maharashtra, Marathi



Work Experience

Mar 2022 - Present

Senior Developer

HUNGAMA DIGITAL ENTERTAINMENT PVT LTD

Working on VAS in frontend systems, to implement various



- PHP
- Boostrap
- HTML
- Html5
- Javascript
- JQuery
- PHP/Mvc Framework, Wordpress developer/
- Angular Js
- Ajax, Javascript, jquery
- Ajax



Personal Information

Date of birth 02-Sep-1991

Gender Male

Address

At Post: Georai Taluka: Newasa District: Ahmednagar Pincode: 414604 Phone (R): 9730594071

City Mumbai

Country INDIA

kinds of fraud

Script like evina integration using frontend technologies.

Sep 2018 - Mar 2022

Senior Software Engineer

Clover Infotech Pvt Ltd, Mumbai

Easy Pay online is a unique payment solution that allows you to make payments for school or college fees, insurance premiums, housing society maintenance bills and lot more. It provides the facility to pay through many payment option and also integration can be done with easypay through web service provided to corporate and multiple modules such as SGB, Agent modules.

Jan 2017 - Apr 2018

PHP Developer

Ginfomedia solutions, Mahim, Mumbai

Understanding client requirement, end to end integration of corporates as per requirements, UI developments and unit testing of all modules after integration.

Oct 2015 - Jan 2017

PHP Developer

Sib Infotech, Malad, Mumbai

Involved in design, development and unit testing Was completely responsible in working with various departments and ensure that the application was delivered with the highest quality.n task detailing and story points.

Was completely responsible in working with various departments and ensure that the application was delivered with the highest quality

Solve complex technical problems which occur during development

Perform effectively and meet the deadlines to ensure that the application are delivered on time.